[Music]
[音乐]
我将向您展示如何制作
I'm going to show you how to make this
相当复杂的父亲圣诞贺卡
当您拉动标签时，它会显示
I'm going to show you how to make this
rather complicated father Christmas card
消息确实需要一些测量
很乖，但我会带领你
rather complicated father Christmas card
and when you pull the tab it reveals the
通过一步一步，以便您可以
自行设计所需的零件
and when you pull the tab it reveals the
message it does take some measuring it
第一是这是基础表
这张纸在这里你看
message it does take some measuring it
is quite fiddly but I'll lead you
另一面，你可以看到何时放
这是插槽，这是插槽
is quite fiddly but I'll lead you
through step by step so that you can
我把它切开了
这是重要的切口
through step by step so that you can
make your own design the pieces you need
切开的东西是你切开的
稍微向后退一点
make your own design the pieces you need
number one is this is the base sheet
卡可以提起并允许条带
如果您要在其中轻松移动
number one is this is the base sheet
this sheet here you look at it on the
写下地带并在周围摇摆
那么它实际上可以卡住，所以我已经
this sheet here you look at it on the
other side and you can see when you put
完成此操作后，我将条带穿过
测量了需要的宽度
other side and you can see when you put
it down here's the slot this is a slot
每个都变了毫米左右
边，然后像
it down here's the slot this is a slot
that I've cut in it there's a slit here
所有这些带子需要加倍
厚度和胶水，所以这是街
that I've cut in it there's a slit here
this is the slit here the important
我已经把它折好了，现在
用胶水将它关闭，我也发现了很长时间
this is the slit here the important
thing with slits is that you cut them
像这样从胶粘中剥离
如果把它们弄平就很好
thing with slits is that you cut them
back slightly at the end so a little bit
平放在桌子上，否则他们可以
倾向于有点退缩或发展
back slightly at the end so a little bit
of card can lift up and allow the strip
某种弯曲，所以有
将胶水涂抹在整个背面
of card can lift up and allow the strip
to move easily within it if you go to
然后将其折叠
然后把它放平放在桌子上
to move easily within it if you go to
write the strip and wobble around and
真的堆出来，你有一个真正的
好的扁条是下一个关键部分
write the strip and wobble around and
then it can actually Jam so the way I've
是其中之一，所以这就像
这中央的位只是宽一点
then it can actually Jam so the way I've
done this I put the strip across it and
比地带，然后其他两个
折起来，剩下两个襟翼
done this I put the strip across it and
measured how wide it needed to be and
在顶部，就在
条带的顶部，以便将三个胶粘在一起
measured how wide it needed to be and
just went a millimeter or so wider each
粘到中间部分
放置它真的很好
just went a millimeter or so wider each
side and then and cut it back as with
干燥，因为这些可怜的被剥夺了
机制你真正的一件事
side and then and cut it back as with
all these strips they need to be double
不想要的是胶水渗出只是牙龈
一切都停止了，并很好地阻止了它的移动
all these strips they need to be double
thickness and glued so here's the street
这是这两个家伙过来
看到折痕在同一点相遇
thickness and glued so here's the street
I've scored it folded it and now just
然后有两个襟翼
上
I've scored it folded it and now just
glue it closed I've also found with long
我们只是被压扁了
坚持到底，然后你坚持下去
glue it closed I've also found with long
strips like this up from gluing them
通过缝隙结束，然后你把
这两个部分穿过那个插槽
strips like this up from gluing them
it's quite good if you smooth them out
压平它们，使它们光滑
它周围，然后胶合在一起
it's quite good if you smooth them out
flat on the table otherwise they can
与顶部齐平，所以这是一个
全带上的变化
flat on the table otherwise they can
tend to sort of back in a bit or develop
您可以在其中拉标签并制作一个
东西滑下页面，这是
tend to sort of back in a bit or develop
some sort of bending and so having
您的运动量
片刻，这似乎正在工作
some sort of bending and so having
smeared the glue all over the back of it
很好，所以这些是另一个
这是这个实际的阵容
smeared the glue all over the back of it
and then then folded it shut
这样我要放两个
两侧都有折痕，因此可以折叠
and then then folded it shut
then yeah put it flat on the table and
只需将卡片的背面变圆
下方留着一点胡须
then yeah put it flat on the table and
really pile it out you've got a really
像这样的胡须
我已经测量过了，所以它应该适合
really pile it out you've got a really
good flat strip the next crucial piece
在那儿，我认为这需要解决
有点像我做的那样
good flat strip the next crucial piece
is one of these so this is a piece like
这种肤色
我剪了
is one of these so this is a piece like
this the central bit is just a tad wider
这些孔在这些，以便
眼睛将通过那里露出粉红色
this the central bit is just a tad wider
than the strip and then these two other
那会留在胡须后面，所以我会
只需将其粘在上面
than the strip and then these two other
bits fold in and there's two flaps left
现在把胡子粘在皮肤上
继续在那里，所以胡须连接
bits fold in and there's two flaps left
on the top and that goes right at the
它下面的胡须，你可以看到
通过我切入的眼孔
on the top and that goes right at the
top of the strip so you glue the three
肤色与眼睛相配
破坏绿色植物的孔
top of the strip so you glue the three
central sections once you've glued into
这样就可以贴在那里
在我做之前，我要坚持下去
central sections once you've glued into
place it's good to just let it really
绿色的一侧将胶水全部倒下
一侧在这里，这与
place it's good to just let it really
dry because with these poor stripped
那里的顶部，所以像
那，我们对此感到满意，或者我们可以
dry because with these poor stripped
mechanisms the one thing you really
也将另一面向下粘
然后这些像这样继续下去
mechanisms the one thing you really
don't want is glue oozing that just gums
整理我可能需要的胡须
修剪一下，使其稍稍对齐
don't want is glue oozing that just gums
it all up and stops it moving nicely
像那样
你知道
it all up and stops it moving nicely
here is these two guys come over you can
把这块胶粘下来，使所有的线
留着眼睛，所以当你拉这个
here is these two guys come over you can
see the creases meet at the same point
你得到扩展名下来，
现在离开这个的原因，所以你
see the creases meet at the same point
and then there's these two flaps stand
可以举起它，现在你标记在哪里
眼睛实际上会进入
and then there's these two flaps stand
up
这一直都在眼前
在这里，然后一路走来
up
we're just pressed up flat you glue this
向下，我们希望眼睛在这里
另一面，所以现在我们可以打开它
we're just pressed up flat you glue this
piece on to the end then you stick this
我们将这两个标记合在一起
就像你可以去一个
piece on to the end then you stick this
end through the slit and then you put
实际上有点宽，这是
眼睛，我们可以将其阴影
end through the slit and then you put
these two pieces up through that slot
然后检查一下，以便关闭
向上推，向下推，你可以看到
these two pieces up through that slot
flatten them out put glue on them smooth
如果您满意的话，眼睛就会动
这样，您已经将它们阴影足够
flatten them out put glue on them smooth
it around and then this glues up pretty
那么你可以将另一面向下
所以你把胶水放在那里
it around and then this glues up pretty
much flush with the top so this is one
当您坚持使用这些
白色的眼睛，它的眼睛和
much flush with the top so this is one
of the variations on the full strip
这是胡须下的胡须
这个白色一直到
of the variations on the full strip
where you can pull a tab and make a
顶部在这里，所以我们必须离开
下拉时眼睛的空间
where you can pull a tab and make a
thing slide down the page this is the
要容纳的冰
当此位下降时，您必须
thing slide down the page this is the
amount of movement you've got at the
确保它没有下降到目前为止
它实际上出现在这里
amount of movement you've got at the
moment so that seems to be working
拉下胡子，现在你已经
这个拉条太长了
moment so that seems to be working
pretty nicely so these are the other
当然你把它推到完全推开
向上的位置，然后将其剪断
pretty nicely so these are the other
pieces this is this actual lineup piece
碰巧我有关于
正确的长度，所以它移动的量是
pieces this is this actual lineup piece
this is going to go like this I put two
完全正确，但是如果您已经
花费了太多时间，所以这个
this is going to go like this I put two
creases on each side so it can fold
当你拉它之前
其实速度太快或眼睛
creases on each side so it can fold
round the back of the card with just a
开始显示，所以您实际上可以
通过放置一块来控制
round the back of the card with just a
bit of a beard sticking out below that's
像这样的一块被卡在
它粘在带子上，当你拉
bit of a beard sticking out below that's
like this this bit of beard here and
它下来要反对这个
针织，使运动停止，所以你
like this this bit of beard here and
I've measured this so it should just fit
可以控制和影响
通过添加东西获得的运动
I've measured this so it should just fit
on there I think this needs to come down
这样比较好切槽
太长，然后使用其中之一来
on there I think this needs to come down
a bit so it's about like that I've made
控制运动，然后掌握整体
事情太短了，所以你实际上不能
a bit so it's about like that I've made
this skin color
让它做您想要的，所以现在您可以
添加您的消息，您知道您可能不会
this skin color
I've cut
想说
圣诞节，你可能想说
I've cut
these holes in this piece so that the
还有其他取决于您的事情
那将适合在那里，然后是最后一个
these holes in this piece so that the
eyes will show through there the pink
要做的就是将这些
喜庆的红军，所以头的宽度
eyes will show through there the pink
that will go behind the beard so I'll
就是这样，然后四舍五入
似乎还可以，所以我会坚持
that will go behind the beard so I'll
just glue that on as well so having
在那我想画一些
功能，所以是的，也许我们会
just glue that on as well so having
stuck the beard on to the skin this now
这里的鼻子或类似的东西
有些眉毛可能会帮助你
stuck the beard on to the skin this now
goes on there so the beard connects that
眼睛周围有点线
可能会有所帮助，这实际上取决于
goes on there so the beard connects that
with the beard below it and you can see
你是你个人的艺术
自然，然后我们也将其作为
with the beard below it and you can see
through the eye holes that I've cut into
底部的红色部分
可以来，你可以衡量它
through the eye holes that I've cut into
the skin tone match up with the eye
像这样它需要稍微上升
当胡须在其上方上下滑动时
the skin tone match up with the eye
holes that are cutting the greenery and
它永远不会超过这个阶段
真的不是那个问题
holes that are cutting the greenery and
so that can be stuck on there just
您可能希望它真正走到
在这种情况下下降到底部
so that can be stuck on there just
before I do it I'm going to stick down
是的，在这上面切了一条缝
我写了一个圣诞快乐
before I do it I'm going to stick down
one side of the green put glue all down
所以在这取决于你，你可以
随便写什么
one side of the green put glue all down
one side here and this goes flush with
说圣诞快乐，您可能想要
说一些您可能想说的话
one side here and this goes flush with
the top there so that's going on like
生日快乐，我不知道你
想说我给你的一个关键是
the top there so that's going on like
that and we're happy with it or we can
拿一支铅笔，非常非常标记
轻轻地将其轻轻拉下
that and we're happy with it or we can
stick the other side down as well and
分数并只标出最低
你可以随书一起写，所以现在你
stick the other side down as well and
then this bits going to go on like this
推回去，那个标记已经
往下拉时消失了
then this bits going to go on like this
line up the beards I might need to just
您写您的信息或其中的任何内容
在这里，你不希望字母是
line up the beards I might need to just
trim that ever so slightly lining it up
低于该标记，以便当
完全在上面
trim that ever so slightly lining it up
like that
你只想要它干净整洁
使其更容易抓住您的标签
you know just that
可以实际得分，因此您可以
得分就在这里，理想情况下，
glue this piece down so all lines up the
做到这一点之前，
然后在背面做，这样
glue this piece down so all lines up the
beard the eyes so now when you pull this
选项卡折叠，因此更容易
抓住它
beard the eyes so now when you pull this
you get the extension coming down and
[音乐]